威尔 · 森坦斯: 所以我们看到 a 函数可以返回
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So we saw there
that A function can be returned
从运行与其他功能,
from the running with other function,
存储在全局标签中，通过新的全局标签在函数中使用它。
stored in the global label, used that in
the function by its new global label.
它与函数的原始运行没有任何关系
And it has nothing to do with
the original running of the function that
从中创建内部功能，然后返回。
from which that inner function
was created, was returned.
现在我们来看看。
Let's now see.
稍微接近的东西。
Something slightly adjacent.
在我们结束之前，我们需要明白的最后一件事。
And the last thing we need to understand,
before we hit closure.
在同一个函数调用中调用一个函数，就像它被定义的那样。
Calling a function in the same
function call, as it was defined.
我看着这个。
I look at this.
我要去拯救外部，还没有做它的任何代码,
I'm gonna save outer,
not do any of its code yet,
运行外部，创建计数器作为0内，存储它。
run outer,
create counter as 0 inside, store it.
保存 incrementCounter 函数，存储它，然后调用该函数。
Save the function incrementCounter
Store it, and then call that function.
然后，看起来，我们要寻找
And then, by the looks of it,
we're gonna look for
不在 incrementCounter 函数中的一些数据。
some data that is not inside
that incrementCounter function.
但是我们要跳出一个层次的外部的呼唤。
But we're gonna step out one
layer to the call of outer.
使用罚款调用同一函数角中的函数。
Calling a function in the same
function corners with a fine.
增量计数器是通过保存 outer 和
Increment counter was defined
with saving the call of outer and
那就马上用。
then use immediately.
马上打电话。
Call immediately.
这会产生非同寻常的后果。
This is gonna have
extraordinary consequences.
还有我们自己，我们在想是什么决定了我跑步的时候
And also ourselves we thinking what
determines the fact that when I run
外层内增量计数器。
increment counter inside of outer.
在增量计数器里面没有找到计数器,
And I don't find counter
inside of increment counter,
我不知道为什么会有存储在外部的计数器。
I'm somehow going to have access
to counter stored in outer.
每个人都知道答案。
Everyone already knows the answer.
那你呢？
Well, do you?
好了我们开始吧。
All right, here we go.
一号线。
Line one.
我们在马太福音第一行做什么,
What are we doing in
line one over to Matthew,
马修今晚我们要做什么？
Matthew tonight What are we doing?
扬声器2: 您正在定义外部函数全局作用域。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're defining
the outer function global scope.
Will Sentance: Beautiful 定义了外部函数。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful define
defining the outer function.
讲者2: 在哪里？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Where?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 让我们称之为全局记忆。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's
call it in a global memory.
为了准确起见，我想告诉你具体是什么
Just to keep precise I wanna
give you what specifically
作用域最持久的东西是在这篇文章的最后。
JavaScript scope's most permanent thing
is towards the end of this piece.
所以现在让我们只说 outer 是在我们的全局执行上下文内存中找到的
So for now let's just say outer is to find
in our global execution context memory in
我们的全球记忆，就在那里。
our global memory, there it is.
好极了。
Excellent.
现在轮到你了 Kayla 我们接下来要做什么？
Now, what do we do next,
over to you, Kayla, we are going to?
说话人3: 执行外部功能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Execute the outer function.
威尔 · 森特斯: 很好，意思是每个人,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent,
meaning everybody,
我们要创造一个全新的-演讲者4: 执行上下文。
we're gonna create a brand new-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 好极了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent, all right.
进入执行上下文，我们去，很酷的堆栈真的很重要，因为我们在这里
Into the execution context we go,
cool stack really important here cuz we're
现在调用函数内部的函数，这样会更有趣。
now calling a function inside of function
so it's always gonna be more interesting.
所以我们有全球性的，总是在底部。
So we've got global as
always on the bottom.
然后我们现在在顶部添加了外部。
Then we have now outer added on top.
很好，很好，准备好了，对吗？
Nicely.
Nice and ready, right?
我自己也很惊讶。
Is this is surprised myself.
在六月，我们去我们的本地记忆彼得，我们首先存储什么？
In June, we go In our local memory Peter,
what are we storing first?
演讲者2: 我们正在存储可变计数器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're storing
the variable counter.
我们的值是0。
We have values 0.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，我知道人们在变量，所以
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
I know people at the variable so
我们可以改变里面的价值。
we can alter the value stored in it.
现在我们到了布拉登旁边的哪条夜线，接下来我们做什么？
Now we hit what night line next
over to Braden, what do we do next?
说话人2: 你在定义函数增量计数器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're defining
the function increment counter.
是的，在哪个执行上下文的本地内存中？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, inside of
which execution context local memory?
只要提醒我们，我知道我们可以看到它，但只要提醒我们。
Just remind us, I know we can see it,
but just remind us.
我们在哪个执行环境中定义它？
We're defining it inside
which execution context?
演讲者2: 内在外在。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Inside the outer.
在外部的执行上下文中,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Inside
outer's execution context,
我们把它保存在外层的执行上下文中。
we're saving it inside of
outer's execution context.
我们在使用它吗？
And are we using it?
是的。
Yeah, we are.
布莱登，接下来我们该怎么办？
Braden, what are we gonna do next?
扬声器2: 你要增加计数器变量。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're going to
increment the counter variable.
是的，我们要执行什么函数？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah we're
gonna execute what function?
瑞典的下一个职能是什么？
What function next Sweden?
是的，所以布拉登看起来像布拉登可能会跳
Yes, so Braden do you see
looked like Braden might jump
直接进入函数，我们保存函数的代码。
straight into the function we
save the code of the function.
计数器加号存储在标签增量计数器下。
Counter plus plus was stored under
the label increment counter.
然后我们继续做什么，布莱登？
And we moved on to do what, Braden?
说话人2: 调用递增计数器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: To call increment counter.
是的，是什么让我们这么叫它的？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
what told us to call it?
说话人2: 括号。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The parentheses.
威尔 · 句子: 括号，确切地说是朋友和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Parentheses,
exactly friends and
我们创造一种全新的水，每个人。
we create a brand new water everybody.
行动联系非常好。
Action contacts excellent.
在它的本地内存中，这变得非常小。
And in its local memory
This is getting very small.
在他当地的记忆里，我打破了我的规则。
I'm breaking my rules
here in his local memory.
很酷的堆栈。
Cool stack.
在冷却的一面会发生什么？
What happens on the cool side down?
我们增加了增量计数器。
We add increment counter.
是的，我们有很酷的增量计数器。
Yeah we got the cool to increment counter.
这就是调用堆栈，因为它是在外部记录的。
Onto the call stack there it is,
because recording it inside of outer.
当我们运行完它，全局我们将返回到外部，对不对？
When we finished running it,
global we'll go back to outer, right?
这是一种很好的记录一切的方式。
It's kind of nice it
keeps track of it all.
好的，现在 incrementCounter 内部的实际代码行是什么
Okay, what is the actual line of code
toward inside of incrementCounter that now
被处决了？
gets executed?
所以你只要告诉我确切的词。
So you just give me the exact words.
讲者2: 描述计数器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: An incriment counter.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，你们都很有想象力。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
you're all very fancy.
直接告诉我,
Just give me the literally,
我只是想说清楚，因为我的名字和我的功能有很大的模糊性。
just to be clear because it's a big
ambiguous with my name of my functions.
那么字面上来说，到底什么样的词才能被运用呢？
So literally what is
the exact words that get run?
确切的数字是多少?-说话人2: 它会加上
What's the exact-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It'll add
一个人对他们的威尔 · 森特斯说: 看,
one to their-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: See,
通讯非常好，但是字面意思是加强计数器。
the communication's so good, but
literally it says counter plus plus.
不，别担心，托德，你的意义远远不止是是计数器
No don't worry Todd, you're being much
more meaningful than just yeah counter
再加上，也就是说要在计数器上加一。
plus plus, which means add one to counter.
好了，该查查了。
Okay, time to do some look up.
我要用绿色笔来查找我要用绿色底片当我抬头看的时候,
I'm gonna use green pen for my lookup And,
I'm gonna use green film when I look up,
我该先去哪里找柜台，马特？
and where do I look for
counter first, Matt?
扬声器2: 你要在增量计数器的上下文中查找。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're gonna look in
the context of increment counter.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，很漂亮。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, beautiful.
我能找到柜台吗？
Do I find counter?
讲者二: 没有 威尔 · 森塔斯: 不，是这样
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, so
接下来我该往哪里看？
where do I look out next?
演讲者2: 上到外部语境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Go up to the outer context.
威尔: 进入外层，我会找到反面吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into outer,
do I find counter?
当然了。
You bet I do.
我找到了计数器，并把它增加到什么马特？
I find counter, and
increment it to what Matt?
讲者二: 一 威尔 · 森特斯: 为了一个人，为了我,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: One.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: To one, what I;m up,
没错。
exactly.
换句话说，现在所有的事情都在暗示着
In other words,
everything would suggest right now
我第一次看我的呼叫栈顶部，没有找到我要找的东西。
that I first looked top of my call stack,
didn't find what I was looking for.
所以我猜，因为我运行的是递增计数器，在 outer 的运行中。
So I guess, because I'm running increment
counter, inside the running of outer.
我该怎么办，我往下走了一层。
What do I do, I went down one layer.
在我的酷栈，失去了外部的权利，听起来是正确的，不是吗？
Down my cool stack and losing the outer
right that sounds right isn't it?
嗯，在我看来是对的。
Hmm, it seems right to me.
我想我从内部到外部运行它看起来并没有错
I guess I'm running it inside of
outside doesn't seem wrong and yet
现在的食物，这是一个真正的谜，是否。
food right now,
that is genuinely a mystery as to whether.
这是一个事实，我正在运行增量计数器在运行的外部
It's a fact that I'm running increment
counter inside the running of outer that
当我在本地内存的增量计数器中找不到计数器的时候给我访问
gives me access when I don't find counter
in local memory of increment counter to go
还是因为我保存了。
out to outers local memory, or
is it the fact that I saved.
外部运行中的增量计数器
Increment counter inside
the running of outer
我定义它，我字面上保存了它的代码在运行的外部。
that I defined it that I literally saved
its code inside the running of outer.
现在，我不知道，实际上我现在不能告诉你。
Right now, I can't tell,
I actually couldn't tell you right now.
所以我用增量计数器做了两件事。
So I did two things with
increment counter inside about.
(1)我在外层运行它。
(1) I ran it inside of outer.
跑进里面的外面，我把它保存在里面的外面。
running inside of outer into,
I saved it inside of outer.
可能是因为我看到了外部世界的内部。
It could be the fact that I
see that inside of outer.
这意味着它在运行时以某种方式有一个连接
That means somehow it has
a connection when it gets run
放在柜台旁边。
to the counter that was
stored adjacent to it.
或者可能是因为我现在在外层运行它。
Or it could be the fact that I
run it inside of outer right now.
我不知道。
I can't tell.
然而，这将是理解闭包的基础。
And yet it's going to be fundamental
to understanding closure.
答案是什么
What the answer to that is